hartists.net 2008-04-11

# Privacy Policy - hArtists

Global Announcement: [hArtists Website Update](http://hartists.net/forum/announcement.php?a=1)  
  
We strongly believe in your right to privacy. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our website, as well as some of the steps we take to make sure this information is not abused by third parties. We hope this document will aid you in making an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us.

## What we Collect

  * When your web browser makes a request for a page on our website, we record the following information, which we may use for research and improving our website: 
    1. The name of the page you requested
    2. The name and vendor of your browser and operating system
    3. Your IP address (usually changes each time you connect to the internet)
    4. The status code, indicating whether the request succeeded or not
    5. How much bandwidth the request used
    6. Your preferred content language for browsing the web
  * When you sign up for an account, we collect further information about you in order to prevent disruption of our services and to help personalize the website for you: 
    1. The nickname or "handle" you used when signing up
    2. A password of your choosing
    3. Your E-Mail address, used to confirm your account
    4. Optionally, the reason why you wanted to sign up for an account
    5. Your IP address
If you opt to register as an artist, we also collect: 
    1. Two sample art submissions which are deleted once your registration is processed
  * We may store cookies on your computer when you make use of certain parts of our website. Cookies are little text files stored on your computer that can be used by the website to store information about your visit. Our cookies expire after fifteen days and are then deleted by your web browser. You can consult your web browser's help file if you would like to manually delete cookies set by this website. 
  * When you make use of communication features (private messages, forums, comments, etc.) we collect the following information you provide: 
    1. A subject entered by you
    2. The message you intend to post
This information is stored in our database and will be backed up. If you decide to cancel your account, this information will be retained to conserve the flow of conversation. 

## Uses

We may use personal information to provide you with services you signed up for, including services that display customized content and advertising. We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our website and services.

Sometimes we may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

Personal information is processed on our servers in the Federal Republic of Germany. In some cases, this may mean that we process personal information on a server outside your own country.  
  
Copyright © 2003 - 2008 hArtists

_Wow, you must be bored if you are reading this..._

About Us | Privacy Policy | Terms of Service | Report Abuse
